Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York (ACUSNY); Records apap003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1938-1992; 5; 13.32 cubic ft.
  - Higher Education Act Reauthorization, (1991), 1989-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Higher Education Forum, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Higher Education (Fiscal Flywheel for Private Colleges), 1984 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - I, 1986; 1989; 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - K, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Lane Press, Inc., 1985 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Legislation: Campus Crime, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Mail Ballot of Membership, 1990 December 13 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Management Issues (Small NYC Colleges), 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Martens, Freda, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Institute for Non Violence, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - New York African American Institute, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - NYS Higher Education Services Corp, 1988; 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - NYS Science and Technology Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Newsletter, 1992 Winter (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - O, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Open Mind, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Office of Business Permits and Regulatory Assistance, 1987 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - P, 1988; 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Part Time Students, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Pinson, Stephanie, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Press Releases, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Purchase Orders, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Statement of Program Priorities, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - R, 1984; 1986; 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Sexual Assault, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Science, 1987-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - State Board of Elections, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Student Financial Aid Committee, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Student Loan Defaults, 1988; 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - T, 1987-1988; 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Tenement Museum, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - U, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Vocational Education Performance Studies, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - VSP, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - W (Miscellaneous), 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Western New York Consortium, 1988; 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Workforce Planning (NYS), 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Xerox Corporation, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - ACUSNY Brochure, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - ACUSNY By-Laws Committee, 1956; 1985-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - ACUSNY History, 1985 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - ACUSNY Plan of Organization, 1985-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Bollam, Sheedy and Torani Co, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Candidates, 1987 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - College Savings Project, 1983 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - College Board Meeting, 1986 May 7 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, General, 1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Dues Assessment Committee, 1985-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Financial Policy Development, Presidential Task Force on financial policy development, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Flier: Higher Education in New York State, 1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Hewlett Packard Laser Jet Printer, 1985-1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Interim Director Norman Kurland, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Insurance, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Mutual Assistance Consult, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Pool of Students Committee, 1985 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Science and Technology, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - State University of New York, Clifton R. Wharton, Jr., Chancellor, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Year 2000 Colloquium, 1985-1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - College Correspondence, Undated; 5.167
    - Colleges with First Letter "A", 1982-1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Colleges with First Letter "B", 1986-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Colleges with First Letter "C", 1980-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Colleges with First Letter "D", 1980-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Colleges with First Letter "E", 1980-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Colleges with First Letter "F", 1984-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Colleges with First Letter "G", 1988-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Colleges with First Letter "H", 1984-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Colleges with First Letter "I", 1984-1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Colleges with First Letter "J", 1982-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Colleges with First Letter "K", 1988 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Colleges with First Letter "L", 1980-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Colleges with First Letter "M", 1980-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Colleges with First Letter "N", 1981-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Colleges with First Letter "O", 1985-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Colleges with First Letter "P", 1984-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Colleges with First Letter "Q", 1988-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Colleges with First Letter "R", 1982-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Colleges that Begin with "S", 1984-1990 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Colleges that Begin with "T", 1985-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Colleges that Begin with "U", 1984-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Colleges that Begin with "V, W, X, Y, Z", 1980-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - State Colleges that Begin with "N", 1985-1989 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - State Colleges that Begin with "S", 1984-1991 (Box 4 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Correspondence with all sectors, Undated; 5.168
    - Association of Proprietary Colleges, 1987-1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - CICU President Mark Lawton, 1987-1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - CICU Annual Meeting, 1988-1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with All Sectors, 1988-1990 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - CUNY: Chancellor Dr. W. Ann Reynolds, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - CUNY: Vice Chancellor Jay Hershenson, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - CUNY: Chancellor J. Murphy, 1984-1989 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - CUNY, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Master Plan Independent Sector, 1988 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - SUNY: Chancellor D.B. Johnstone, 1988-1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - SUNY: Act. Chanc. J. Komisar, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - SUNY: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State of New York files, Undated; 5.169
    - Commissioners Postsecondary Advisory Council, 1989 March (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Commissioners Postsecondary Advisory Council, 1989 October 31 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Commissioners Postsecondary Advisory Council, 1990 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Commissioners Postsecondary Advisory Council, 1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Commissioners Task Force Report on the Teaching Profession, 1988 May (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Liberty Scholarship, 1988 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - New Compact for Learning, 1991 (Box 5 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Contracts, Leases and Policies, 1983-1989 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Federal Legislation and Education in N.Y. State First Draft 1992 Regents brochure, Undated (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Governor's Office of Employee Relations, 1984-1987 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - INFO (NYS Association of 2 Year Colleges, Inc), 1988 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Nursing, 1988 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Regents Brochure, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Regents Statewide Plan, 1990 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Report of the Temporary State Commission on Future of Postsecundary Education in New York State, 1977 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - SED, 1984-1991 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - SED: Donald J. Nolan, 1985-1992 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Science Conference Planning, 1989 November (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Science Conference (ACUSNY): Planning & Notes, 05/30/1989 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Science Conference (ACUSNY): Rockefeller Institute, 1989 May 30 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Science Conference (Governor's conference), 1989 December 5 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - State Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Stateside - ACE (American Council on Education) publication vol. 1, number 1, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Foundations, Undated; 5.170
    - AT&T Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1984-1989 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Exxon Foundation, 1984-1988 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation, 1985-1991 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Foundations, 1988 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Mellon, Andrew W. Foundation, 1984-1989 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Morgan Guaranty-Trust Company of New York, 1984-1985 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - New York Times Foundation, Inc., 1988 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - The Pew Charitable Trust, 1989 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1984-1986 (Box 7 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Out-of State Associations, Undated; 5.171
    - AAHE (American Association of Higher Education), 1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - AAUP, 1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - ACE-Correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - ACE State Multisector Association, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - American Management Association (T. Horten), 1985 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - American Association of State Colleges & Universities, 1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Association of Colleges of the Mid-Hudson Area, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Association of President of Public Community Colleges, 1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Association of Texas Colleges & Universities, 1987-1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Business Council, 1988-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Council for Institutional Leadership, 1989-1992 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Hudson-Mohawk Association of Colleges & Universities, 1988-1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - List of Statewide Associations, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Long Island Regional Advisory Council on Higher Education, LIRACHE, 1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Maine Higher Education Council, 1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Middle Atlantic States Association, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - National Association of Corporate & Professional Recruiters, 1990 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges, 1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - National Center for Academic Achievement and Transfer, 1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - National Center for Postsecondary Governance & Finance, 1986-1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - National Center on Education & the Economy, 1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - National Society for Internship and Experimental Education, 1990 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - National Student Exchange, 1986-1987 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - New Jersey Association of Colleges & Universities, 1982 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - NYS Association of Two Year Colleges, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - New York State Financial Aid Administrator's Association, 1990 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - New York State School Boards Association, 1985-1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Ohio College Association, 1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - PA Association of Colleges & Universities, 1988-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Partnership of Service Learning, 1989 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Rochester Area Colleges, 1988 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - State Associations of Colleges with Public & Private Members, 1986-1990 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Vermont Higher Education Council, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 34)
- Membership Files, 1943; 1949-1991; 6; 1.33 cubic ft.
  Contains correspondence with individual institutions, (especially concerning the acceptance of members into the Association), membership lists, and the membership report, 1991.
  - Academy of Aeronautics, 1966 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 1)
  - Adirondack Community College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 2)
  - Albany Business College, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 3)
  - Adelphi University, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 4)
  - Bank Street College of Education, 1956-1961 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 5)
  - Bard College, 1959-1970 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 6)
  - Barnard College, 1953-1977 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 7)
  - Berkley Schools, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 8)
  - Boricua College, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 9)
  - Borough of Manhattan Community College, 1964-1977 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 10)
  - Bronx Community College, 1958-1976 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 11)
  - Cayuga Community College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 12)
  - Clarkson University, 1959-1970 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 13)
  - Colgate University, 1950 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 14)
  - College of Insurance, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 15)
  - College of Mt. St. Vincent, 1958 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 16)
  - College of New Rochelle, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 17)
  - College of St. Rose, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 18)
  - Cooper Union, 1953-1968 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 19)
  - Corning Community College, 1960-1976 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 20)
  - Culinary Institute of America, 1974-1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 21)
  - D'Youville College, 1973 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 22)
  - Dominican College of Blauvelt, 1962-1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 23)
  - Dowling College, 1970-1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 24)
  - Dutchess Community College, 1960-1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 25)
  - Elizabeth Seton College, 1961-1989 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 26)
  - Five Towns College, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 27)
  - Fordham University, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 28)
  - Geneseo Community College, 1967 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 29)
  - Hardwick College, 1949 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 30)
  - Harriman College, 1964-1984 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 31)
  - Hebrew Union College, 1955-1978 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 32)
  - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1951 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 33)
  - Hofstra University, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 34)
  - Hostos Community College, 1972-1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 35)
  - Hudson Valley Community College, 1955-1970 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 36)
  - Hunter College, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 37)
  - Interboro Institute, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 38)
  - Ithaca College, 1951-1958 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 39)
  - Jamestown Business College, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 40)
  - Jefferson Community College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 41)
  - Juilliard School, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 42)
  - Kingsborough Community College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 43)
  - Laboratory Institute of Merchandising, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 44)
  - Ladycliff College, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 45)
  - Le Moyne College, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 46)
  - Manhattan School of Music, 1955 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 47)
  - Manhattan College of the Sacred Heart, 1953-1975 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 48)
  - Mannes College of Music, 1963-1966 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 49)
  - Maria College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 50)
  - Maria Regina College, 1965-1988 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 51)
  - Marialle College, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 52)
  - Marist College, 1955-1959 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 53)
  - Marymount College, 1969-1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 54)
  - Marymount Manhattan College, 1961-1975 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 55)
  - Mercy College, 1953-1959 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 56)
  - Missionary Training Institute, 1955 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 57)
  - Mohawk Valley Community College, 1955-1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 58)
  - Molley College, 1960-1977 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 59)
  - Monroe Business Institute, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 60)
  - Monroe Community College, 1964-1971 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 61)
  - Mount St. Mary College, 1958-1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 62)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 63)
  - Nassau Community College, 1960-1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 64)
  - New York Chiropractic College, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 65)
  - New York Institute of Finance, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 66)
  - Niagara County Community College, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 67)
  - Niagara University, 1963 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 68)
  - Olean Business Institute, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 69)
  - Onondaga Community College, 1964-1971 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 70)
  - Paul Smith's College, 1956-1959 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 71)
  - Polytechnic Institute, 1974-1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 72)
  - Pratt Institute, 1952-1977 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 73)
  - Queen's College, 1950 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 74)
  - Queensborough Community College, 1960-1974 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 75)
  - Robert Wesleyan College, 1965-1975 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 76)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1955-1967 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 77)
  - Rockefeller Institute, 1955 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 78)
  - Rockland Community College, 1961-1975 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 79)
  - Rosary Hill College, 1948-1974 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 80)
  - Russell Sage College, 1959-1969 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 81)
  - Sancta Maria College, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 82)
  - School of Visual Arts, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Membership Files), Folder 83)